Change... history?
Yes... I want you to show me.
That this unsalvageable ruin...
That this tragedy devoid of all hope...
...can be made to never happen.
Is that even possible?
I've heard people say
history will correct itself.
Did the people who propose that
change time and show proof?
W-Well...
No matter how large the world is,
the only one who can interfere with time...
...is me, Kurumi Tokisaki.
In which case, that which you see
with your eyes before you...
...is the only one truth that there is.
I'll really be able to save Origami?
That all depends on you.
All right.
Let's do this, Kurumi.
"Itsuka"
What do you think you're doing?
Cutting through this way is faster.
Who are you...?
Uh, um... Sorry!
Hey! Come back, you!
Shido?
Shoot, I can't be wasting time here!
What now? What now?!
"Itsuka"
Shido?
Hello.
Did anyone sketchy come through here?
Huh? I haven't seen anybody.
Yeah? That's odd...
Um...
Huh? Oh, never mind!
Say hi to your mom for me!
Phew, that was close.
Good thinking there.
Yeah...
Can't believe Natsumi's transformation
powers actually came in handy.
Looking like that, no one will
bat an eye seeing you in the past.
Sure, but how do I go back to normal?
It's cute, so why even bother?
You know what?
That must be Kotori's...
Seems that way.
Let's hurry!
A girl defies time and changes into a devil.
All by himself, a boy
contests a repeat disaster.
"Episode Nine:
'Tengu City, Five Years Ago'"
That's...
Phantom!
Origami!
Metatron!
Chase after her.
Right!
Origami!
It's me! Listen!
It's useless!
At this rate...!
Origami! Origami!
Origami!
Huh?!
Dad... Mom...!
Shido?
I'm all right. More importantly...
Wha...?!
Angel?
I will...
...never forgive you!
I'll kill you...
I swear, I'll kill you!
Someday, I will!
What the hell?
What the hell... is this?!
I see...
For someone like Origami to become like this,
I knew something significant
had to have happened.
She's gone?!
Yod Bet must have reached its limit.
She went back to her original time.
No way...
Then, Origami...
She wasn't able to change history?
This can't be...
Origami!
A-Are you okay, Origami?
Dad... Mom...
I...
Origami!
I'm sorry, I... I...
Who are you?
It's all right! It'll be all right!
Origami, someday you're realize it.
All of this, the truth...
But please don't forget! You're not alone!
What are you saying...?
All of your sadness and hate--
I'll carry all of it for you!
If you're lost, lean on me!
When something happens and
it's too much, rely on me!
Everything... It's okay
to dump everything on me!
So... So...
Don't let despair take over you!
Thank you.
Who are you anyway?
Huh? Uh, um...
I'm Shido Itsuka.
I live in the neighborhood.
Shido Itsuka.
Did you mean everything you said?
Yeah, I meant it.
I see.
In that case, this is the last time I cry.
But,
it's also the last time I smile.
Eh?
All my sadness and joy...
All the fun in my life, I give to you.
But, this anger... This anger is mine alone.
I'll kill it...
That angel...
No matter how long it takes.
No matter what it takes.
Origami?
So, carry all of it for me.
Until I kill the angel.
Until then.
So that's how it was...
How ironic to happen this way.
You're...
How disappointing.
I'm sorry. You even used Yod Bet
on me to fix all this...
That's not what I'm referring to.
Huh?
The one who killed her parents
was Origami herself.
This whole situation wouldn't have
happened if not for my Zaphkiel.
And that's a fact which is
incredibly upsetting to me.
Still, it's not like you used Zaphkiel
hoping for this to happen, right?
Of course not.
Anyway, it doesn't matter
'cuz it's all over now.
Is that what you think?
True. As far as that world
is concerned, what's done is done.
However, I was just presented a method
to overturn that a moment ago.
Presented? By who?
By you a few dozen minutes from now.
The future me?!
Why would I do something like that?
Because the method isn't available to you
who returned to your original time.
So for me right now, there's still
a way I can save Origami?!
Yes, it's not over just yet.
Kurumi!
Indeed. It's about time we
sacked this shithole of a world.
Right. I'll do anything to save Origami!
Attaboy, that's the spirit.
So? What's the method?
It's quite simple in theory.
We'll just have you try it again.
Huh? What do you mean?
The main reason you were unable
to do anything to stop Origami
was because you had no idea
what would happen to begin with.
That's true, but...
So now that I know, you want
to use Yod Bet on me again?
An interesting guess,
but I'm afraid that's impossible.
As it stands now, I'm simply
sharing your senses.
I can't physically interact with you.
Then, what?
There's one thing...
One single method that only I know.
Is this the place?
Yes, without a doubt.
But, I don't...
Well, well.
It's not every day that a guest
stumbles upon us here.
Kurumi!
For someone to know me and my name...
You...
Who the hell are you?
You, five years ago?
Yes, five years ago I
was also near the scene.
What were you doing there?
Just checking what the blaze was about.
I figured a Spirit might be
part of an inferno that size.
I see. Then if you were
there five years ago...
Yes. You'll have me shoot you.
With Yod Bet.
Kurumi, I need your help!
Do not move without my permission.
I can't guarantee you'll live.
I'm Shido Itsuka. I came
from five years in the future,
Kurumi, using your powers!
If this is some sort of joke--
This isn't a joke!
Please! Listen to me!
My goodness, the old me
sure is quite cautious.
Shido, do you think you could
have that me touch you?
All right.
Did you say something?
Kurumi, you can keep that gun on me,
but will you come touch my hand?
Kurumi says she wants to talk.
I said that?
Is it odd if I start with
"Long time no see," old me?
Interesting... You have
my voice, so that's a start.
What is this all about?
I see.
You're saying you want me to point
Yod Bet at him and shoot?
Yes, that's precisely what I want.
Very well.
Really?!
Because it's me asking, I can't refuse.
Now, come to me, Zaphkiel!
Your time has come!
Zaphkiel, Yod Bet.
All right, shall we proceed?
Yeah.
Origami, this time, I'll...
I wish you good luck.
Shido?
Looks like it worked.
Let's go change the world.
I assume you have a plan then?
You're letting this all go to waste!
Don't blame me! I haven't had time to think!
Right now, you and I know
exactly what's about to occur.
So how about preventing Origami
from realizing who killed her parents?
I considered that, too, but it doesn't
change the fact that her parents die.
Besides, as long as her parents
are killed by the hands of a Spirit,
Origami's grudge might fall
on someone else instead.
On Kotori, who caused the inferno...
Or otherwise, Phantom,
who gave her that power.
What are you thinking, Shido?
Wouldn't it work out if Origami appears
but there's no enemy in sight?
That's possible, but...
There's something I want to try.
"West Tengu Park"
Shido, you're creeping around like a pervert.
Shut up.
I imagine you understand this, but...
You mustn't interact with Kotori, you know.
"West Tengu Park"
Yeah, I get that.
I can't tamper with history more than needed.
The one I came here to save is Origami.
Shido.
It's here!
Try to restrain yourself.
Kotori, I'm sorry!
Hey!
I've been waiting for you, Phantom.
It can't be... You're...
Why are you...?
Wait, you know me?
Shido.
I'm on it!
That reaction was unexpected.
Is that someone you know, Shido?
Can't say I know anyone who
censors their whole body.
I never thought your big plan
would be to chat with Phantom.
Got a problem?
No, I think that's very like you to try.
But I can't say I recommend it.
That one is impossible to predict.
Do you know Phantom or...?
Phantom!
Phantom, is it?
Is that the name I was given?
Sorry for running off like that.
I thought it better to do this away from her.
I see... I knew you were...
Is that what you look like?
This isn't my real appearance.
I can't show you what
I truly look like just yet.
Do you know who I am or something?
I do.
I know you well.
So?
Is that all you wanted?
You used a time-travel bullet to come here.
It wasn't just for fun, was it?
How do you...?
In that case, I'll get straight to the point.
I need you to disappear!
Is that a poetic way to
say you came to kill me?
This isn't about killing!
I just want you to hide, and fast!
I see.
Sorry, but my answer is "No."
There're still a few things I have to do.
Hold on! Origami is about to--
What's wrong, Shido?
Why... does this feel so familiar?
When the time is right, let's meet again.
And then...
...I will never let go.
I won't make that mistake again.
Are you okay, Shido?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Who was she?
Don't tell me...
Origami!
Don't, Origami!
Shit!
I won't let...
...that happen again!
I will... make it change!
Origami... Origami!
Dad... Mom...
Don't, Origami!
No use. It's too late!
Shit, Origami!
Shido!
Ah, thank goodness...
Huh?
Wasn't I...?
Kurumi? Kurumi!
Did I... do it?
Did I save them?
Origami and... her parents?
"Episode Ten:
'Another World, Another Girl'"